My mommy always said
there were no monsters.
No real ones.
But there are.
She's perfect.
Careful.
Two centimeters.
Okay. Okay.
Yeah. Ready with that amnio.
And...
...there it is.
But be careful.
Jesus.
Clamp.
What about her? Can we keep her alive?
How's the host?
Doing well.
Sew her back up.
Excellent work. Everybody.
- How is our Number Eight today?
- Appears to be in good health.
- How good?
- Excellent.
As in completely off our projected charts.
Look at the scar tissue.
See the recession?
- This is from three days ago?
- Exactly.
Well, this is good.
This is very good.
You're gonna make us all very proud.
No.
Don't! I'm all right!
Now try this.
- Hand.
- Close.
Glove.
Number Eight?
- Fruit.
- Good, cherries.
- It's unprecedented.
- Totally.
She's operating at
a completely adult capacity.
- What about her memories?
- There are gaps.
- Some degree of synaptic dissonance.
- You know this.
She's freaked.
It has connective difficulties,
caused by a biochemical imbalance...
...causing emotional autism.
Certain reactions--
Wait a second. It has memories.
Why does it have memories?
Well, I'm guessing,
but inherited memories...
...passed down generationally at a genetic
level by the aliens, like its strength.
Plus a highly evolved form of instinct.
An unexpected benefit
from the genetic crossing.
Oh, I see. Well, of course.
Stupid me. Of course.
An unexpected benefit of the genetic
process! I didn't even think of that.
Let's try this one.
Ripley?
Ripley, what is it?
Ripley? Ripley?
- You're not thinking termination?
- Oh, boy, am I thinking termination.
We do not perceive this to be a problem.
Ellen Ripley died
trying to wipe this species out.
For all intents and purposes,
she succeeded.
I'm not anxious to see her
taking up her old hobbies.
- That won't happen.
- We won't tell her.
Oh, I see.
And that's supposed to comfort me.
Identification, please.
Please try again.
Thank you, General Perez.
The bottom line is, she looks at me funny
one time, I'm putting her down.
Okay, as far as I'm concerned,
Number Eight...
...is a meat byproduct.
Her Majesty here is the real payoff.
- When does she start producing?
- Days.
Less, maybe.
- We need the cargo.
- I told you, it's on its way.
Fork.
- Fuck.
- It's "fork."
How did you...?
How did we get you?
Yes.
Hard work. We used blood samples
from Fiori 16, on ice.
Where you died.
We've remade you. We cloned you.
Fiori 16.
Does that ring a bell?
Are you remembering something?
Does it grow?
Yeah. Very rapidly.
- It's a queen.
- How did you know that?
She'll breed.
You'll die.
Everyone in the company will die.
"In the company"?
Weyland-Yutani.
Ripley Eight's former employers.
A Terran Growth conglomerate. They
had defense contracts under the military.
Oh, they went under decades ago, Gediman.
Way before your time.
Bought out by Wal-Mart.
Fortunes of war.
I think you will find that things have
changed a great deal since your time.
I doubt that.
We're not flying blind here, you know.
This is United Systems Military,
not some greedy corporation.
Well, it won't make any difference.
You're still gonna die.
How do you feel about that?
I wish you could understand
what we're trying to do.
The potential for this species
goes way beyond urban pacification:
New alloys, new vaccines.
Nothing like this we've ever seen
on any world before.
You should be very proud.
I am.
And the animal itself:
Wondrous.
The potential, unbelievable.
Once we've tamed him.
Roll over? Play dead?
Heel?
You can't teach it tricks.
Why not? We're teaching you.
Hey, son, I'll give you
my authorization code.
It's E-A-T-M-E.
I'm sorry, sir, could you repeat that?
Little prick.
You know, no matter
how many times you see it...
...the sight of a woman all strapped up
in a chair like that just...
What?
Just bring us in on a 3-0 descent,
would you? And ride the parallel.
- Darling, it is done.
- Good girl.
You want anything there, trigger?
Yeah. How about a cup of coffee?
Anything else while your mouth's warm,
I mean?
A little milk.
Hey, don't cut thrust till about 600 meters.
We'll give them a little scare.
Vriess! Call!
Batton down, we're gonna dock.
- Hey, Call?
- Yeah?
What has two thumbs, one eye...
...a pink tongue...
...and screws like a god?
What?
Two thumbs, one eye, a pink tongue...
...and screws like a god?
What?
Time to enjoy some of
the general's hospitality, Christie.
Great. Army food.
Yeah, it'll do till we get
the family wagon up to spec, I reckon.
Yeah.
That is, if the natives are friendly.
- How's that?
- Good.
Are we expecting any trouble?
From Perez, I doubt it. But you
never know, we've been there before.
What is wrong with you?
Just a little target practice.
Vriess isn't complaining.
Goddamn it.
Johner, you son of a bitch!
Come on, man, you didn't feel a thing.
You are an inbred motherfucker,
you know that?
I'll take the knife back now.
Call, forget it.
He's been sucking down
too much home-brew.
The knife.
Son of a bitch!
Don't push me, Call.
You hang with us for a while...
...you'll find out I am not the man
with whom to fuck.
It's about time we started associating
with a better class of people.
I am Father.
Welcome to the USM Auriga.
Step forward for contraband
and weapons search.
Please report any infectious diseases
to the medical officers.
Levels 7 through 12
are off-limits to civilians.
Thank you for your cooperation.
Go.
- Get your hands up, please, sir.
- What?
Could you get your hands up, please?
There are no weapons
allowed onboard, sir.
My own recipe.
Way more dangerous.
Nice welcome, Perez.
What the hell is this?
Are you afraid the six of us are gonna
hijack your damn ship or what?
Just the minor concern that
one of your asshole crew members...
...is gonna get drunk and put a bullet
through the hull. We happen to be in space.
No shit.
How you been?
Wanna check the chair?
Elgyn, these were very, very hard
to come by.
So was our cargo.
You're not about to plead poverty on me,
are you, general?
No. I'm just saying,
very few people deal in cash nowadays.
Just the ones don't like to keep
business records. Yourself, for example.
- Drink, Elgyn?
- Constantly.
I'm gonna take a wild guess here, general,
but I'm thinking...
...whatever you got going on here,
it ain't exactly approved by Congress.
Who's the new filly
you got onboard, Elgyn?
Call?
Little girl playing pirates?
She makes an impression.
She is severely fuckable, ain't she?
Mighty handy with a monkey wrench too,
I might add.
I think Vriess has got
a bit of a light in his eye for her.
Fine little ass like that make a man walk,
you know what I mean?
Mind you, I think she's just a tad curious
about this little transaction of ours.
I mean, I can't say as I blame her.
It's awfully cloak-and-dagger stuff.
It's a military operation.
Really?
Correct me if I'm wrong,
but I was under the impression that...
...most army medical labs don't have to
operate outside of regulated space.
What do you want, Elgyn?
What can I do for you?
- Me?
- Yeah.
Two days' bed and board.
Vriess might wanna snag a part
here or there.
Whatever. I mean, if it's not imposing.
I don't see any problem.
- A couple of conditions, though.
- Conditions.
Not you, nor any of your...
...formidable crew members...
...will go anywhere near restricted areas.
Rule number two:
- No trouble. Good behavior.
- Good behavior.
- No fights.
- No fights?
Please direct cargo to medlab center,
Area G.
Follow the lit path.
Do not deviate.
Cargo status stable.
Life forms intact.
Stasis uninterrupted.
Medlab center is off-limits to civilians.
Thank you.
- Hey.
- Oh, please.
You know I can't lay off the tall ones.
How you doing?
How about a little one-on-one?
What do you say?
You got some moves on you, girl.
Man.
You know, if you don't wanna play
basketball, I know some other indoor sports.
Come on, now, give me the ball.
Okay. I got a new game.
Tag.
Ripley!
Ripley.
You've had enough fun.
What the hell are you?
Something of a predator, isn't she?
Yes, she continues
to make us all very proud.
We're coming up on
just one minute and 30 seconds left...
...to order this one-of-a-kind
collector's item.
Jesus Christ, Johner,
what did you put in this shit? Battery acid?
Just for color.
So, we're a fast learner.
- Now here's a fine item...
- This is a really good show, man.
It's from the Gut Cutters
Celebration Collection...
...makers of premiere knives
and edge wear.
The knife has a stainless-steel blade...
...perfect for any use.
The handle is made from authentic
antique plywood and stained in...
Woman, that shit is not easy to come by!
Why don't you take a walk outside?
- Great!
- I'm so sorry.
Shit, if bitches can't handle this shit,
bitches should stay away from this shit!
Fucking bitch.
Identification, please.
Please try again.
Thank you, General Perez.
Well?
Are you gonna kill me, or what?
There's no point, is there?
They've taken it out of you.
Where is it? Is it on the ship?
You mean my baby?
I don't get it. If they took it out,
why are they keeping you alive?
Well, they're curious. I'm the latest thing.
Look, I can make it all stop.
The pain, this nightmare.
That's all I can offer you.
What makes you think
I would let you do that?
Who are you?
Ripley, Ellen. Lieutenant first class.
Number 36706.
Ellen Ripley died 200 years ago.
You're not her.
I'm not her?
- Who am I?
- You're a thing, a construct.
They grew you in a fucking lab.
And now they brought it out of you.
Not all the way out.
I can feel it.
Behind my eyes.
I can hear it moving.
You gotta help me stop this thing
before it gets loose.
It's too late.
You can't stop it.
It's inevitable.
Not as long as I'm around.
You'll never get out of here alive.
I don't care.
Really?
I can make it stop.
Go on, get out of here.
They're looking for you.
I think you're gonna find that this was
very ill-advised. Where are her friends?
- They're in the mess hall, sir.
- Well, you find them now. Quietly.
- What the hell is going on here?
- It smells like a double-cross, boss.
Where's the other one? With the chair?
Don't ever touch me. Ever!
Wanna tell us what this is?
- Wanna tell me who you're working for?
- What?
- Wren, they got nothing to do with this.
- To do with what?
Do you know what the penalties
for terrorist activity are?
No terrorists in my crew.
Call, something you wanna tell me?
I don't care whether you knew or not. You
brought a terrorist onboard a military vessel.
And as far as I am concerned,
you all die with her.
Do you understand?
Yeah.
I understand.
Christie.
Freeze!
Stop! Drop your weapons!
And you, drop that piece of shit!
Or I blow his head off!
- I can't do that, man.
- Drop it now!
- Can't, they're attached.
- I'm not fucking with you!
You're all under arrest for a Code 8,
which is concealed weapons...
...and a Code 12, which is murder.
Release Dr.--
- Kiss my ass.
- Put down your weapons!
Everybody okay?
Real easy, soldier boy.
Security, there is a serious problem
in the mess hall.
You lie to me now, little girl...
...I will cut your throat and
leave you here to die. Understand?
- This is Security, Section 2.
- Hello?
- We do not read you.
- Goddamn. Hello?
- We do not copy you. Please repeat.
- Hello?
Please repeat.
Gediman!
He's conducting illegal experiments,
breeding...
- Ice the goddamn mole.
- Listen, he is breeding an alien species.
Dangerous. If it gets loose,
it'll make the Lacerta plague...
- ...look like a fucking square dance.
- Shut up!
Listen.
Your attention, please. Security breach.
Medlab, Level 15.
Let's get back to the Betty. The doctor
and soldier boy can see us to the door.
- What about Vriess?
- Fuck Vriess.
Your attention, please.
Unauthorized opening of Cage 3.
Unauthorized opening of Cages 5...
...7, 8, 10.
- Move it! Now!
- Evacuation.
- Go! Go! Go!
This is not a drill.
- Evacuation.
- Get on board!
Your attention, please.
Nonhuman presence detected.
Levels 21, 23.
Twenty-seven.
Fourteen.
Level 38.
Level 39.
Evacuation. Proceed to lifeboats.
This is not a drill.
Thank you for your cooperation.
I'll give you holes, you slimy bastard!
Move it! Go!
- Final lifeboat ready for launch.
- Get on board!
- Go!
- Complete evacuation now.
No!
Grenade.
Alert. Alert.
Evacuation incomplete.
Civilian presence detected in Area H.
Warning,
main vessel declared uninhabitable.
- Elgyn, come on. Let's move, man.
- Yeah.
Elgyn? Elgyn, where are you?
Elgyn, where are you?
Elgyn!
- Oh, my God. Elgyn!
- Elgyn?
Elgyn?
Easy, Hillard!
- Give me a hand. Give me a hand here!
- Get him up! Get him up!
- Come on, let's get him up.
- Move out of the way!
Shit.
- What the fuck did this?
- What's in this place?
- Call, get down!
- What the fuck is that?
Don't shoot! It's in front of the hull!
- What is that?
- Come on, man, time to go. Time to go.
Get back!
Time to go!
Come on, Call!
Open the goddamn door!
We can't open it! We can't open that.
We can't open the door!
- We gotta go back!
- I'm not going back. You go back.
What the fuck?
Was it everything you hoped for?
Leave him alone.
What do we do now, man?
Same thing we're doing.
We get the hell out of here.
What if there's more?
I say we stay here, man.
Let the army guys deal.
- Where the fuck are the army guys?
- They're dead.
- Then we don't need this asshole anymore.
- Step back!
- No, you step back.
- Stop it!
You got no authority here!
Doctor, that thing that killed my partner.
- That's your pet science project?
- Yes.
- Let me do him right now, man.
- I should let him do you right now.
How many more are there?
Twelve.
Twelve?
There'll be more.
So who do I have to fuck
to get off this boat?
I can get you off.
Maybe not the boat, but...
Let's get out of here.
No, wait a second here.
She was the host for these monsters.
Wren cloned her
because she had one inside her.
She's not human.
She was part of his experiment
and she will turn on us in a second.
- I don't give a shit what she is.
- She's too much of a risk.
- We have to leave her.
- She comes.
- We can't trust her.
- I don't trust anyone.
If we're gonna survive this mess,
we all stick together. Agreed?
Hillard, we gotta go.
It's not over. We gotta get to the Betty.
Make a nice souvenir.
- I can't believe you did that.
- Did what?
Killed one. It's like killing your own kind.
It was in my way.
Oh, man.
Who were you expecting? Santa Claus?
I thought you were toast for certain, man.
Where's Elgyn?
- Shit.
- What if they're all over the Betty?
All the activity's been in the F sector.
Why would they move?
They won't.
If they send anyone out, it'll be...
...here.
Where the meat is.
Yeah. Well, I say if we wanna make
any decent time, I say we ditch the cripple.
- No offense, man.
- None taken.
Nobody is left behind.
Not even you, Johner.
- What's the quickest way out of here?
- After the cooling tower, there's an elevator.
It runs from the top of the ship
down to engineering, Level 1 deck.
- Take us straight to the dock.
- Sounds reasonable. Let's do it.
We're moving.
- What?
- The ship is moving. I can feel it.
The ship has stealth-run.
There's no way you can tell.
- She's right.
- The ship's been go since the attack.
It's a standard emergency procedure.
That's right. Any serious problem,
the ship autopilots back to home base.
And you were planning on
letting us know this?
Nobody asked.
What's home base?
Earth.
- Great.
- Bastard.
Earth? I'd rather stay here
with the things, man.
- How long until we get to Earth?
- Three hours almost.
We gotta blow the ship.
Call! You're not blowing this ship.
Not while we're on it, okay?
We get out of the ship,
you do as you please, all right?
Earth, man. What a shithole.
It's clear.
Hey, Ripley.
I heard you, like,
ran into these things before.
- That's right.
- Wow, man.
So, like, what did you do?
I died.
Not that way!
Ripley.
Ripley, come on.
Ripley, we got no time for sightseeing here.
Ripley, don't.
Kill...
...me.
Kill me.
Don't do it, Ripley.
Don't do what?
What's the big deal, man?
Fucking waste of ammo.
Let's go.
It must be a chick thing.
Am I dreaming or is this not
the shit we brought with us?
Yeah. It's the same shit.
It stinks in here, man. Let's keep moving.
Get away from me!
- Drop the rod.
- Get away from me!
- Do it!
- Get away from me.
Get away from me.
Who are you people?
- What's happening here?
- Calm down.
What's happening here is we're
getting the fuck off this ghost ship, okay?
Ship? What ship?
Where am I?
I was in cryo, right?
On my way to Xarem, right?
Work crew for the nickel refinery, right?
I wake up...
I know I don't understand.
Oh, God. I--
I saw-- I saw horrible things.
Look, you're coming with us.
It's too dangerous for you here.
Leave him.
Fuck you. We're not leaving him here.
He's got one inside of him. I can smell it.
Inside me?
Inside me? What's inside me?
Hey, I don't want one of those things
birthing anywhere near my ass.
- It's a bad risk.
- What's inside me?
- Look, we can't just leave him here.
- You came here to stop them from spreading.
- What's inside me?
- Gotta be a process. Can't you stop it?
- We've got no time for that.
- We can't do it here. The lab's out of order.
I could do him.
Back of the head. Painless.
It might be the best way.
What's inside me?
- No, there's got to be another way.
- What if we freeze him?
What's in-fucking-side me?!
A parasite!
A foreign element.
There's a monster in your chest.
These guys hijacked your ship...
...and they sold your cryotube
to this human.
And he put an alien inside of you.
It's a really nasty one.
And in a few hours, it's gonna
burst its way through your rib cage...
...and you're gonna die.
Any questions?
Who are you?
I'm the monster's mother.
He comes with us, we freeze him on
the Betty, the doctor can remove it later.
- Fine by me.
- Since when were you in goddamn charge?
Since you were born without balls.
Ease off, people!
All right, you come with us.
You might even live.
Get twitchy on me and you'll be shot.
Let's move out.
It's a mess down there.
Is this the only way?
Vriess. We gotta lose the chair.
I know.
- Kawlang maneuver, right?
- Yeah. Just like old times.
Yeah.
Must be the cooling tanks.
Somebody must have opened the valves.
The nasties couldn't have done this,
could they?
We're at the bottom of the ship.
We have to go through the kitchen.
Maybe 90 feet.
To the freight elevator on the other side.
- I don't like it.
- What's to like?
- This sucks!
- Wren, are you sure about the distance?
Yes.
- You ready to get wet, partner?
- Yeah.
Hey, will your weapons fly underwater?
Yeah, they're disposables.
They can take it.
Disposables?
Hey, I heard about those. Yeah.
- How many rounds?
- Twenty.
Split points give you a good hole,
even if it's smaller caliber.
That's cool.
They're big with hitters
because you throw them away after the job.
Nobody likes to throw away a weapon
they're attached to, you know?
Yeah.
Guess I don't have to tell everyone
to take a deep breath.
Hey, Christie, do me a favor.
When we hit the surface on the other side,
no backstroke, okay?
Jesus Christ!
They set a goddamn trap.
It's a goddamn ambush!
Distephano!
It won't break. Give me your weapon.
You really are way too trusting.
No!
You killed her! You bastard!
I'll get you!
Father, lock the door.
Christie! Climb!
Climb! Come on!
Come on!
It's jammed! Move it!
It's jammed!
Get off my foot, bitch!
Johner!
Get off me! Get off me!
Die, motherfucker!
Do it, man!
Real nice party, ain't it?
Christie!
No!
What are you doing? Don't do it!
Don't!
We can make it!
No!
Damn.
This way.
Come on!
Baby, am I glad to see you.
I was sure that asshole got you.
Are you hurt?
I'm fine.
- You got body armor on?
- Yeah. Come on.
You took it in the chest. I saw it.
You're a robot?
Son of a bitch! Our little Call
is just full of surprises.
I should've known.
No human being is that humane.
I thought synthetics
were supposed to be logical.
You just a big old psycho, girl.
- You're a robot?
- You're a Second Gen, aren't you?
You're an Auton.
Robots designed by robots, right?
That's right, I remember.
They were supposed to revitalize
the synthetic industry.
Instead they buried it.
They don't like being told what to do.
The government ordered a recall.
Now, I heard...
I had heard that only a few--
Just a few had gotten out in time.
Man, I never thought
that I would see one!
Great. She's a toaster oven.
Can we leave now?
- How long before we land?
- Just under two hours.
Hey, Vriess, you got a socket wrench?
Maybe she just needs an oil change.
I'm sorry. Access denied.
- I can't believe I almost fucked it.
- Yeah, like you never fucked a robot!
You know, if Wren gets in the computer,
he could screw us.
- We gotta find a terminal.
- No, there's no console on this level.
- We'd have to go back.
- Well, we can't go back.
- And I don't know Wren's access codes.
- Help me.
Call.
No, I can't.
Right. You're the new model droid.
You can access the mainframe by remote.
No, I can't. I burned my modem.
We all did.
Call, you can still patch in manually,
you know that.
There's ports in the chapel, up there.
Call.
- You're programmed for that?
- Don't make me do this.
Don't make me make you.
I don't wanna go in there.
It's like my insides are liquid.
It's not real.
Get over it. You can blow this ship
before it reaches Earth...
...and kill them all.
Just give us time to get out first.
- Damn it.
- Anything?
Hold on.
Breach in Sector 7, Sector 3.
Sector 9 unstable.
Engines operating at 41 percent.
Eighty-six minutes until Earth dock.
We burned too much energy.
I can't make critical mass.
I can't blow it.
Then crash it.
I'm okay. I'm okay.
Really.
I feel good.
Ground level recalibrated.
New destination: 7-6-0-4-0-3.
Uninhabited quadrant.
Braking system's offline.
Deceleration increase.
Time until impact
now 43 minutes, 8 seconds.
Try to clear us a path to the Betty.
And start her up.
Please wait.
Emergency override
in console 45V, Level 1.
It's Wren. He's almost at the Betty.
Father, locate the power drain. Report.
Father? Father?
Father's dead, asshole.
Intruder on Level 1.
All aliens, please proceed to Level 1.
You got a mean streak.
Damn it.
- Let me see.
- Don't touch me.
Come on.
You must think this is pretty funny.
I'm finding a lot of things funny lately.
But I don't think they are.
Why do you go on living?
How can you stand being what you are?
Not much choice.
At least there's part of you
that's human.
I'm just...
Look at me.
I'm disgusting.
Why did you come here?
To kill you. Remember?
Before the recall...
...I accessed the mainframe.
Every dirty little covert op
the government ever dreamed up is in there.
And this, you, the aliens,
even the crew from the Betty.
I knew if they succeeded,
it'd be the end of them.
Why do you care what happens to them?
Because I'm programmed to.
You're programmed to be an asshole?
You're the new asshole model
they're putting out?
Come on.
I couldn't watch them do it.
I couldn't let them annihilate themselves.
Do you understand that?
I did once.
I tried to save people.
It didn't work out.
There was this girl.
She had bad dreams.
I tried to help her.
She died.
Now I can't even remember her name.
I guess we're almost there.
Right.
- Do you dream?
- I-- We have neural processors that-- Yes.
When I sleep, I dream about them. It.
Every night.
All around me. In me.
I used to be afraid to dream,
but I'm not anymore.
Why?
Because no matter how bad the dreams
get, when I wake up it's always worse.
- It's not so far now!
- God, I'm so tired!
Sleep when you die, man.
Oh, no. This is bad, right?
I think we're near the nest.
- Well, then, we'll go another way.
- We don't have time.
- We got nearly 90 minutes.
- Not anymore.
What are you saying?
- What did you do, robot?
- Let's go. Come on.
Hey! You wanna die here with your
little brothers and sisters, that's cool.
But I plan to live past today.
If this little hunk of plastic
is pulling any shit...
...I'm gonna kill her!
Kill you!
Does that compute?
Or do I have to draw you a schematic?
Hey!
You want another souvenir?
- How far are the docks?
- A hundred yards.
Ripley?
Come on.
Ripley, we have to go.
I hear them. I hear them.
They're so close.
- Ripley.
- It's the queen.
She's in pain.
Ripley!
Wait!
Oh, my God.
We gotta be moving. The best thing
we can do is pray for a quick death.
Come on. Come on.
- It's not right.
- I've been saying that all day.
It's up to you now, Call.
I need you to patch into the ship again,
and open the hatch.
Johner, we should put Purvis
in the freezer now.
All right, little buddy.
Nap time.
Nobody moves, or I put a cap
right where this little droid's brain is.
- Distephano, take the weapons.
- Begging your pardon, sir, but fuck you!
Oh, fine. Then I kill her...
...and you kill me, and we all die...
...and nobody goes home!
Now drop the weapon.
Then this little synthetic bitch
is gonna plug into the Auriga...
...and she is gonna take us
right back to home base...
...according to the standard
emergency procedures.
- No, she's not.
- Are you crazy?
You still wanna bring those things
back to Earth?
- Haven't you been paying attention today?
- The intellectual speaks.
- Listen, if you don't--
- Don't you ever shut up?
Why does nobody listen to me?
I told you, at first everything was normal.
The queen laid her eggs.
But then she started to change.
She added a second cycle, so...
So...
...this time there is no host.
There are no eggs.
There is only her womb...
...and the creature inside.
That is Ripley's gift to her,
a human reproductive system.
She is giving birth for you, Ripley.
And now she is perfect!
You are...
...a beautiful, beautiful butterfly.
No!
No. No.
Look.
Look, beautiful, beautiful little baby.
Look, it thinks you're its mother.
Come on.
Civilian vessel online.
Emergency departure authorized.
All right, she's hot. I'll open the Auriga's
air locks. Pull the holding clamps.
Right, I just need to find
the vertical thrust lock.
- Are you sure you guys can fly this thing?
- Yes.
- Launch status is go.
- No!
Ripley.
- Hey.
- I thought you were dead.
Yeah, I get that a lot.
- Why are we still here?
- I'm just finding the manual override.
- For chrissake.
- Hey, Ripley.
Good memory. Excuse me.
- Ripley's back, man.
- Is that it?
Nope.
You can't fly one of these things too,
can you?
Are you kidding?
This piece of shit is even older than I am.
Goddamn it! We still got breach.
The hatch.
- I closed it.
- I've fixed the hatch a hundred times, man.
I'll get it. I'll get it.
Approaching Earth's atmosphere.
Window of departure now 46 seconds.
Call? We have to go.
Call.
We've gotta get out of here.
Window of departure now 20 seconds.
Grab on to something, Call.
We're out of here.
Come on, baby.
This thing is gonna fall apart.
Pressure's unstable!
Go help Call turn on the auxiliary pump.
Distephano?
Come on. Step on it.
Hey! I'm not the mechanic here, Ironside.
I mostly just hurt people.
Shit.
Call!
Call, get back up here.
Call! Call!
Ripley. Hey, Ripley!
Johner, where are you, you son of a bitch?
Get on it, bastard.
- What am I supposed to do?
- Grab the sticks.
Put her down.
Ripley!
I'm sorry.
USM Auriga will impact in five seconds.
Four.
Three.
Two. One.
Thank you.
- What's burning?
- Us!
Shit! You're right.
So this is Earth, huh?
This is Earth.
It's my first time here.
I suppose the military'll be
sniffing around here pretty soon.
Bet you're not too anxious to see them.
Not really.
You know, a person could get pretty lost
around here if they wanted to.
What do you think?
What should we do?
I don't know.
I'm a stranger here myself.
[ENGLISH - US]